let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "1. Which of the following user-defined header file extension used in c++??",
    answer: "h",
    options: [
      "hg",
      "cpp",
      "h",
      "hf"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "2. Which of the following is a correct identifier in C++?",
    answer: "VAR_123",
    options: [
      "VAR_1234",
      "$var_name",
      "7VARNAME",
      "7var_name"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " 3. Which of the following type is provided by C++ but not C?",
    answer: "bool",
    options: [
      "double",
      "float",
      "int",
      "bool"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 4,
    question: "4.What is the size of wchar_t in C++?",
    answer: "Based on the number of bits in the system",
    options: [
      "Based on the number of bits in the system",
      "2 or 4",
      "2",
      "4",
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "5.Which is more effective while calling the C++ functions? ",
      answer: "call by reference",
      options: [
        "call by object",
        "call by pointer",
        "call by value",
        "call by refrence"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "6. Which keyword is used to define the macros in c++? ",
    answer: "#define",
    options: [
      " #macro",
      "#define",
      "macro",
      "define",
  ]
  },
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "7. What is Inheritance in C++?",
  answer: " Deriving new classes from existing classes",
  options: [
    " Deriving new classes from existing classes",
    " Overloading of classes",
    " Classes with same names",
    " Wrapping of data into a single class"
  ]
  },
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "8.What is meant by a polymorphism in C++?",
  answer: " class having many forms",
  options: [
    "class having only single form",
    "class having four forms",
    " class having many forms",
    "class having two forms"
  ]
  },
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "9. Which of the following constructors are provided by the C++ compiler if not defined in a class? ",
  answer: "All of the mentioned",
  options: [
    "Copy constructor",
    "Default constructor",
    "Assignment constructor",
    "All of the mentioned"
  ]
  },
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "10.What is the benefit of c++ input and output over c input and output?  ",
  answer: "Type safety",
  options: [ 
    "Both Type safety & Exception",
    "Sequence container",
    "Exception",
    "Type safety"
  ]
  },
  
  ];